My AirPods fell out of my pocket. They
ejected. One landed here
and the other one went down the hole.
>> You dropped your AirPods?
>> Do you see it?
Do you see it or is it gone?
>> It's gone.
>> Oh, man.
Well, that sucks. You know what else
sucks? For Jennifer Lopez,
I'm not a New Yorker.
>> You have to be born in New York to be a
New Yorker. Everybody wants to claim our
city, but you have to be born in New
York. You have to be born in the one of
the five boroughs
to be a New Yorker.
>> Now, I have a bit of a hot take for
Jennifer Lopez.
Okay.
All right, this is This is my hot take
back to Jennifer Lopez. This is
controversial.
I completely
agree with J. Lo.
>> What's your name?
>> My name is Zephyr.
>> Zephyr, where are you from?
>> I'm from New York.
>> Okay, do you think you have to be born
in New York to be a New Yorker?
>> I think you can live here long enough to
be a New Yorker, but
>> Now, there was a time when I would have
disagreed with J. Lo. See, I would have
said, "I've lived in this city for
almost three decades. I've lived here
since I was a teenager. This city's all
I know. I've probably lived in this city
longer than you have, J. Lo. You left
when you started to blow up. I'm I'm
here."
But, that view changed when I had kids.
>> [screaming]
>> Watching your kids grow up in this city,
you realize they're just a different
They're just a different person. They're
a different breed. Your most formative
years as a little kid, you grew up here?
That makes you a very special, very
different kind of person. I'll never be
that New Yorker.
>> Do you think you have to be born in New
York City to be a New Yorker?
>> No, not really.
>> Why do you say it with such confidence?
>> Because I've been here since 1982.
>> Since 1982?
>> I've been on Wall Street since since
1990.
>> But you weren't born here.
>> No.
>> But you're a New Yorker.
>> Yeah, absolutely, 100%.
>> I appreciate that.
>> Absolutely. Are you kidding me?
>> What's your name?
>> I'm Tony.
>> Tony, I'm Casey. Nice to meet you.
>> Nice to meet you, Casey.
>> You see, guys like Tony and me, people
who weren't born in this city, it's more
like we were adopted by this city. And
because of that,
we have to earn our stripes.
>> You earned your stripes.
>> Believe me, from the time I got I got I
I got off the plane.
>> [music]
>> Casey, nice stuff. What the
Now, earning your stripes as a New
Yorker is a responsibility I take
extremely seriously. And every once in a
while, I'm honored with an
acknowledgement
of my assumption of that responsibility.
This morning is one such day.
No one said this, but for me, this
morning I'm being honored.
>> [music]
>> I'm I'm not getting my own ticker tape
parade. There's no mayoral ceremony with
a crowd where they hand me a golden key.
It's not that kind of honor.
But in my opinion, this is no less This
is no less significant.
There it is. That's it, right there. You
see this clock right here?
That is the Seth Thomas Tower Clock. The
Seth Thomas Tower Clock is the only
mechanical clock
in all of New York City. And once every
week or two weeks or something, it has
to be manually wound.
And this woman named Victoria, who's in
charge of this whole plaza here called
Bogardus Plaza,
she picks the people who get to wind it.
And today, I'm that person.
What an honor.
>> [music]
>> Hey.
>> I'm Tory.
>> Nice to meet you, Tory.
>> Nice to meet you, too.
>> I'm Casey.
>> Chris, good to meet you.
>> Chris, hi.
>> I'm Caitlin.
>> Caitlin? [music]
>> Nice to meet you, Chris.
>> Aw, she made it.
>> You know what's so funny? I saw it on
Instagram, and I immediately uh called
him. I'm like, "You have to wind the
clock. You're perfect for winding the
clock." Yeah.
>> Okay, so what happens now?
>> Dun da da da!
Um we teach you how to wind the clock.
So, the first thing is a clock lesson.
>> [music]
>> How do I get one of those keys?
No, it's not going to happen. Okay.
Oh my goodness.
Wow.
So, when we're cranking it, we're
raising that weight up.
>> you're going to raise it up, and you're
probably going to raise it up about to
here.
>> This is the crank, and the crank goes on
there.
What do you think?
>> It's really cool. You know I like old
stuff.
>> Did you touch it?
>> Yes.
>> Is it cool?
>> It's hot.
>> Do you want to touch it, George?
>> [music]
[music]
>> Did you know that this is the only
manual clock in New York City?
>> No. No.
>> Yeah.
>> No. I've never seen it open.
>> I did my winding. I brought This is the
weight and I brought the weight from
down here to up here and then the weight
falls and that's what makes it twist.
>> [music]
>> So Jennifer Lopez, I might not be the
New Yorker
that was born in New York, but I got to
wind the clock
and that's got to count for something.
>> Where do you live now? You live in
California? You live in
>> I live in LA.
>> LA?
>> Mhm.